{
    "Exam1": {
        "id": 1,
        "quesNum": 5,
        "Question1": {
            "Question": "Assisted living residences provide all of the following, except:",
            "Option1": "Housing.",
            "Option2": "Complex medical care.",
            "Option3": "Help with personal care.",
            "Option4": "Social activities.",
            "Correct Answer": 2
        },
        "Question2": {
            "Question": "What does the CCA need to remind the client about during rehabiliation?",
            "Option1": "Progress.",
            "Option2": "Disabilities.",
            "Option3": "Strengths and weaknesses.",
            "Option4": "Limits.",
            "Correct Answer": 1
        },
        "Question3": {
            "Question": "Which are cultural influences?",
            "Option1": "Shelter, nutrition, security and affection.",
            "Option2": "Comfort, caring, loving and trust.",
            "Option3": "Respect, compassion, empathy and sympathy.",
            "Option4": "Language, values, beliefs, customs.",
            "Correct Answer": 4
        },
        "Question4": {
            "Question": "Who can delegate tasks to CCAs?",
            "Option1": "Doctors.",
            "Option2": "Other CCAs.",
            "Option3": "Registered nurses.",
            "Option4": "Therapists.",
            "Correct Answer": 3
        },
        "Question5": {
            "Question": "Which of the following statements about autonomy is correct?",
            "Option1": "It is a fundamental ethical principle.",
            "Option2": "It means limited choice.",
            "Option3": "There should be laws to protect client rights.",
            "Option4": "It means unlimited choice.",
            "Correct Answer": 1
        }
    },
    "Exam2": {
        "id": 2,
        "quesNum": 5,
        "Question1": {
            "Question": "Lori and Eleanor have been caring for their ill grandmother for several years and need a break. Which service should they look into?",
            "Option1": "Respite care.",
            "Option2": "Hospice care.",
            "Option3": "Long-term care.",
            "Option4": "Group home care.",
            "Correct Answer": 1
        },
        "Question2": {
            "Question": "When does rehabilitation start for an affected person?",
            "Option1": "When s/he is admitted to restorative care.",
            "Option2": "When s/he seeks hospital care.",
            "Option3": "When s/he first seeks health care.",
            "Option4": "When the physician writes the order.",
            "Correct Answer": 3
        },
        "Question3": {
            "Question": "What is ethics?",
            "Option1": "A process by which a nurse authorizes another health care provider to perform certain tasks.",
            "Option2": "The principles that guide us when deciding what is right and what is wrong, and what is good and what is bad.",
            "Option3": "A process by which the CCA performs certain tasks.",
            "Option4": "Personal attributes that should guide the CCA's work and conduct.",
            "Correct Answer": 2
        },
        "Question4": {
            "Question": "What is personal accountability?",
            "Option1": "Willingness to accept responsibility and to explain your actions, inactions or omissions, intentions and decisions.",
            "Option2": "Shelter, nutrition, security and affection or physical, safety, love and belonging and self-esteem and self-actualization",
            "Option3": "Report what you witnessed to your supervisor.",
            "Option4": "Respect, compassion, empathy, sympathy, competence and self-awareness.",
            "Correct Answer": 1
        },
        "Question5": {
            "Question": "Care providers are:",
            "Option1": "Paid formal people providing care.",
            "Option2": "In the best health possible.",
            "Option3": "Unpaid informal people providing care.",
            "Option4": "People who serve meals to clients.",
            "Correct Answer": 1
        }
    }
}